Finding Aid for the Lamar Alexander Papers - Photographs
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series I: Governor’s Papers
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Proclamation, National Jaycee Week; Don Sundquist, John Duncan; Jimmy Quillen, Tom Garland, Jim Henry and Governor Alexander, January 9, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Murfreesboro School Visit; Bradley Model School, January 10, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Proclamations, January 14, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Henry County and Paris Task Force Meeting, January 15, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Chester County Task Force Meeting; Crockett, Bells, and Alamo Task Force Meeting, January 16, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Press Conference; Troop Court of Honor (1954), January 18, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Sumner County Task Force Meeting, January 22, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Lecture Series, Vanderbilt University, January 23, 1985 (Box 16)
    - (2 Folders) State Board of Education Conference, Education Board Collage, January 25, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Tullahoma Task Force; Governor’s Office Interns, January 29, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Fayette County Task Force; Tipton County Task Force; Governor Alexander and Charlie Daniels, January 30, 1985 (Box 16)
    - (2 Folders) Governor’s Budget Address; Dyer County Task Force, January 31, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Gov. Alexander and Selective Service Officials; Proclamations, February 5, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Willowbrook School Students, February 7, 1985 (Box 16)
    - St. Bethlehem School Visit, Clarksville, February 8, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Swearing in of Claims Commissioner, February 12, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Presentation of Belt Buckle, Ned McWherter, February 13, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Education, Kettering Foundation Meeting, February 15, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Swearing in of Dale Kelley; Education Study Group; Senator Riley Darnell and Boy Scouts, February 19, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Representative Benny Stafford and Lenoir City High School Students; Harlan Mathews and Presentation of Alvin C. York Rifle; Anna Belle O’Brien, Jim Henry and Four Interns, February 20, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Visit Gray Elementary School and ETSU, February 22, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Conservation Achievement Awards Banquet, February 23, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Lamar Alexander Headshots, February 26, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Representative Bob Harrill and Bradley County Chamber of Commerce, February 27, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Keel Hunt Headshots; Randy McNally in Legislature; Grahamwood Elementary School Visit, Memphis, February 28, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Industrial Bank of Japan Group; Swearing in of Bill Jones, Commissioner of Safety, March 1, 1985 (Box 17)
    - (2 Folders) State of the State Address and Collage Photo; Stephanie Chivers Headshot; John Crisp Headshot, March 4, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Girl Scouts; Remarks to Tennessee Tomorrow Students; Governor Alexander with Susan Cope, March 5, 1985 (Box 17)
    - C. Smith, P. Kendrink, Marc Lavine Headshots, March 6, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Debby Patterson Headshots, March 12, 1985 (Box 17)
    - (Contact Sheet), March 14, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Bob Weaver Headshots, March 15, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Representative Cliff Frensley and Cub Scouts, March 18, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Maryville Citizens; Proclamation for Auctioneers Week; Students from Joelton Middle School, Project Pencil Week, March 19, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Senator Shockley and Representative Ed Moody and John Hay School Students, March 20, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Senator Buzz Elkins and Campbell High School Students, March 21, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Visit to Gibson County Schools; Revenue; Military Presentation of Flag, March 22, 1985 (Box 17)
    - (2 Folders) Nissan Sentra Celebration and Parade through Plant, Collage; Commissioner Bill Long; Lamar Alexander Headshots, March 26, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Homecoming Coordinators Meeting; Senator Person and Christ Methodist Day School Students; Tennessee Association of Elem. School Principals Presentation of Southeastern Friend of Education Award, Charles Peavyhouse, March 27, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Presentation of Colonel Certificate, Dr. Curtis Hutson, March 28, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Commissioner Wade and Sumner County Students; Proclamation, Disney Day, March 29, 1985 (Box 17)
    - (2 Folders) Bill Signing (Credit Life Bill); Representative Ray Clark and 4-H Group, April 1, 1985 (Box 17)
    - George Kelley and ETSU Students, April 2, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Senator Curtis Person, April 3, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Visit to Claiborne County Schools, April 4, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Barbara Mandrell before Legislative Committee Speaking on behalf of Seat Belt Bill, April 9, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Proclamations; Eagleville Cub Scouts; MargueriteW. Sallee Headshot, April 10, 1985 (Box 17)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Representative Don Ridgeway and Proclamation; Representative Randy McNally, Ned McWherter and CSEC Students, April 11, 1985 (Box 18)
    - (2 Folders) Oak Ridge and Roane County School Visits; News/Press Conference for Department of Correction Taskforce, April 12, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Alcoa High School Students; Humboldt Elementary School Students; Bill Signing SB 382/ HB 340 (Intergovernmental Relations); Salute to Roy Acuff; Stewart County Republican Women, April 17, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Tullahoma Schools Visit; Freshman Legislators Reception; Tennessee Finalists for NASA Teacher in Space Project, April 18, 1985 (Box 18)
    - (Contact Sheet), April 19, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Proclamations; 3 Star Awards; Salute to Eddy Arnold, April 23, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Representative Charles Severance and Karns Middle School Students; Representative Randy McNally and Walton Ferry Elementary School Students; Organ Donor Recipient Reception and Proclamation, April 24, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Greene County Task Force Meeting; Morristown, Hamblen, and Greene County School Visits; ETSU; Hamblen County Task Force Breakfast, April 26, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Press Conference; Photo with Robert L. McElrath and Joel Shore; Tennessee Homecoming ’86 West Tennessee Rally, Jackson, April 30, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Bolivar Central High School Beta Club; Bill Signing; Finalists for Presidential Scholars Program; Representative John Tanner; Farragut Jr. High School Students; Oak Hill School Students; Medina Elementary School Students, May 1, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Meeting with Casper Weinberger; Barton Hawkins and Governor Alexander, May 3, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Astronaut Rhea Seddon Presents Governor Alexander with Tennessee State Seal Carried into Space, May 8, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Senator Ray Albright and Snow Hill Elementary School Students, May 9, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Bill Signings, May 13, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Representative Cliff Frensley and Grassland Elementary School Students; Julia Green School Students, May 14, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Eagleville Elementary School Students, May 15, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Empire Motor Company Representatives; Happy Valley School Students, May 16, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Carroll County Luncheon; School Visits: Clarksburgh School, Camden Elementary School, Central Elementary School, McKenzie High School, West Carroll Primary; Carroll County Vocational Center, May 17, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Vice President George Bush Visits Nashville and Grand Ole Opry; Governor Alexander in Knoxville and Maryville, May 18, 1985 (Box 18)
    - May 18-19, 1985 Vice President George Bush Visit (Box 18)
    - Bill Signing (Right to Die), May 20, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Douglas Adult Cooperative Shelter Workshop, May 21, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Bill Signing (Right to Die); Operation CARE and the All American Buckle Up Kickoff, May 23, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Proclamations; Presentation of Certificates; Paul Funkhouser, May 29, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Reception for Commissioner Sammie Lynn Pruett, May 30, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Swearing in of Marguerite W. Sallee, Commissioner of Human Services, May 31, 1985 (Box 18)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Boy Scouts, June 14, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Education-Tennessee Honors Program; Blair School of Music; Administrative Academy, June 15 -21, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Commissioner Marguerite W. Sallee and Governor Alexander; Department of Human Services; Capitol Restoration Committee, June 17, 1985 (Box 19)
    - (2 Folders) Bill Signing; Presentation of Certificates of Appreciation, June 18, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Bill Signing HB 731; Interns from the Banner, June 19, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Red Tape Cutters, June 25, 1985 (Box 19)
    - (4 Folders) Meeting of School Leaders; Three Teachers of Better Schools Career Ladder Program, June 26, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Governor’s Schedule – No Photos, June 28, 1985 (Box 19)
    - (3 Folders) Tennessee Claims Commission; Presentation of Report from Task Force on Youth, Alcohol, and Drug Abuse, July 2, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Corrections, Turney Center, July 3, 1985 (Box 19)
    - International Marketing, Toyota; Governor Alexander in Classroom, July 8, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Bill Hamby, July 11, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Bob Weaver Swearing in Judge Bill Koch; Chinese Runners with Commissioner Long, July 12, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Presentation of Flag; Proclamations; Peaches and Raleigh Anne Blank; Bill Signing of HB 495/SB 797 (Child Sexual Abuse), July 16, 1985 (Box 19)
    - TPAC Rehearsal for Governor’s School for the Arts Concert, July 17-18, 1985 (Box 19)
    - March of Dimes Poster Child, July 18, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Governor’s Schedule – No Photos, July 22, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Group from Carter County, July 23, 1985 (Box 19)
    - The Tennessee Society of Association Executives Luncheon, July 25, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Prairie Home Companion, July 27, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - (10 Folders) Tennessee Welcomes Saturn Corporation, Spring Hill, Press Conference, Plans, Models, New Plant Site, July 27-31, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Service Awards; Bill Long, July 31, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Visit to White’s Creek High School, August 19, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Carolyn Miller and Governor Alexander, August 20, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Zane Whitson, Bill Long and Others, August 21, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Brad Reed, Corry and Lyn Stevens, August 22, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Miss Tennessee American Co-ed; Three Star Awards, August 26, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Announcement of Clinch and Powell Task Force, Cumberland Gap, August 28, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Proclamation for United Way, August 29, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Visit to Johnson County School; Visit to Evans Elementary School; Visit to Unicoi County School; Spring Hill State Trooper; Mayor Jones and Spring Hill County Officials at Residence, September 3, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Visit to Elkton Elementary School; Governor Alexander and Former Governor Hunt; Tennessee Homecoming Trivia Game, September 4, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Mitsui Bank Signing; Visit to Sweetwater Elementary School; Visit to Madisonville High School; Ambassador John Matlock, September 5, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Visit to Alamo Elementary School; Visit to Bells Elementary School; Visit to Caywood Elementary School; Visit to Crockett County High School; Visit to Lexington High School, September 6, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Governor Alexander, Commissioner Bill Long, and Sharp Manufacturing Representatives, September 10, 1985 (Box 20)
    - (2 Folders) Governor Alexander and Commissioner Steve Norris, Comprehensive Correction Plan Press Conference; Tennessee Government Executive Institute Awards, September 16, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Capitol Restoration Committee Reception; Commissioner Bill Long and Kantus Corp.; Swearing In of Kathy Celauro; Dinner for William Hoglund, Saturn, September 17, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Tennesseans’ Outdoors Commission, September 19, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Employment Security, Warren Neel, October 11, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Pleasant View Christian School Students; Steve Riley, October 22, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Representative Riley Darnell, October 23, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Family Portrait, October 25, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Management Conference; Bill Long and Bronson Ingram; 20 Year Certificate, October 28, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Visit to Dyersburg High School; Opening of Doubleday Distribution Center, October 29, 1985 (Box 21)
    - (2 Folders) Reception for Governor Bai; Dedication of Silver Coronet Band Gazebo in Lynchburg, October 30, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Chinese Representatives; Swearing in of Don Jackson, Commissioner of Finance; Swearing In of Dale Kelley, Commissioner of Transportation; Swearing In of Warren Neel, Commissioner of Employment Security, October 31, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Signing of Executive Order Creating the Martin Luther King, Jr. Tennessee Holiday Commission, Coretta Scott King, November 1, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Luncheon with Gerald Ford, November 4, 1985 (Box 21)
    - (3 Folders) Governor’s Address, Special Session on Corrections, House Chambers, November 5, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Governor Alexander Serving Thanksgiving Lunch, November 6, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Tom Lawrence and Boy Scout Troop; Meeting with White House Fellows; American Education Week, November 7, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Board of Regents Meeting, November 8, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Unveiling of Vietnam Veterans Memorial, November 10, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Representative Don Ridgeway; Freshmen Legislative Caucus, November 12, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Lunch with the GOP County Chairmen; John Carpenter and Others; School Group, November 13, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Governor’s Conference on ECD, November 14, 1985 (Box 21)
    - All American Buckle Up Week Signing Ceremony; Southern Regional Infant Mortality Task Force, November 19, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Saturn Conference, November 20, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Bridgestone Representatives; Meeting with Education Staff; Flag Raising Ceremony, November 21, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Governor’s Address to TISL, November 22, 1985 (Box 21)
    - (3 Folders) Honey Alexander at Church with Children; Keel Hunt and Visitors; The Tennessee Sampler; Walt Massey, November 25, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Grand Ole Smokies Christmas Tree at Residence, December 2, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Murfreesboro Campus School Performance, December 3, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Bob Burleson in Front of the Christmas Tree; Ray Albright and Carl Wallace, State Chairman of Employees Support Guard and Reserve; Westwood Jr. High Performance; Janice Mashburn Headshots, December 5, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Press Conference, December 6, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Franklin Middle School Performance; John Parish Headshots, December 10, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Press Conference; Presentation of Certificate to Susan Simmons, December 11, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Clarksville High School Performance, December 12, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Good Luck Party, December 13, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Commissioner Robert L. McElrath; Julia Green Students and Christmas Tree; Gallatin High School Performance, December 17, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Representative Cliff Frensley and Students, December 18, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Legislative Christmas Breakfast; David Stringfield; Debby Koch; Daisy King; Carl Wallace; Dickson County High School Performance, December 19, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Commissioner Walker and Dairy Trophy; Opening of Tunnel; Christmas Luncheon, December 20, 1985 (Box 22)
    - Bell Ringing Ceremony, Capitol Grounds, December 31, 1985 (Box 22)
    - Governor Presents Tulip Poplar Tree to the City, January 4, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Governor Alexander and Representative Jim Henry, January 6, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Summit of Superintendents Meeting, January 7, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Linda Rendtorff, January 9, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Maryville Greenbelt Park Dedication; Walk on Highway 67 and 91; First Tennessee Development District Homecoming ’86 Kickoff; Blount County Homecoming ‘86, January 11, 1986 (Box 22)
    - (2 Folders) Press Conference for Bicentennial Parkway Trust Fund, January 15, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Press Conference for Cleaner Highways; Luncheon with United Way Leaders; Governor Alexander and Winfield Dunn, January 16, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Proclamations; Tennessee School/College Collaborative, TSU; Southern Folk Art Exhibit Reception, Tennessee State Museum, January 22, 1986 (Box 22)
    - State of Education Address, Tennessee Press Association, January 24, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Governor’s Task Force on Day Car; Decatur County Executive, January 28, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Coalition for Scenic Beauty, January 29, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Announcement of Alex Haley Book about Tennessee, January 30, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Certification Teachers, February 3, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Zane Whitson and Members of the Unicoi County Task Force; Martha Olsen; Ben Atchley, Buddy Scruggs and Interns, February 4, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Lenoir City High School Students, February 5, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Bill Signing; Governor Alexander, Bill Clinton, and Ambassador de Margerie, February 6, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Remarks at Kiwanis Club; Swearing In of Linda Rendtorff, Commissioner of Personnel, February 7, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Presentation of Picture, February 10, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Winner of State Poster Graphics and Journalism Contests, February 12, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Governor Alexander, Ed Shea, and Jim King, February 13, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Tennessee Sports Hall of Fame Awards, February 14, 1986 (Box 22)
    - State of the State Address, focus on New Highways, February 17, 1986 (Box 22)
    - West Tennessee Democratic Caucus; Representative Pete Drew and Presentation of Picture; Governor Alexander with Ronnie Greer; Representative Wolfe and Others, February 18, 1986 (Box 22)
    - (2 Folders) Senator Kyle and Danny Thomas Reception for St. Jude Board; Lee Munz and Shoney’s Representative; Governor Alexander and Tennessee Children’s Dance Ensemble, February 19, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Rep. Art Swann and Lanier Elementary School Students; Governor Alexander and American Airlines Representatives, February 20, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Governor Alexander with Bill Dance and Bass Tournament; Governor Alexander at USA Today Plant for USA Today Homecoming ’86 Edition Reception, February 21, 1986 (Box 22)
    - (4 Folders) National Governor’s Conference in Washington, DC, Governor Alexander Accepts Statue of Liberty Replica Gift from French Ambassador During NGA Winter Meeting, with Bill Clinton; Proclamation Signing for Selective Service Awareness Month; Governor Alexander and Dick Clark with Urgent Highway Needs Map; Luncheon at Governor’s Residence, February 26, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Governor Alexander, Bill Long and Mr. Song, Consul General of Korea, February 27, 1986 (Box 22)
    - AACTE Annual Meeting, Chicago, February 28, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Governor’s Address to Tennessee Tomorrow Students, March 4, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Bill Signing with Senator Ford; ‘Pollution Prevention Pays’ Awards Luncheon; Girl Scouts; Representative Maria Peroulas and Family; Presentation of Country Music Tape, March 5, 1986 (Box 22)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - (6 Folders) Sesquicentennial Tribute at the Alamo, San Antonio, Texas, March 6, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Presentation of Homecoming ’86 Doll to Honey Alexander, March 7, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Presentation of Carroll County Three Star Award; Central High School Students; Visit to Rock Creek Elementary School; Tennessee No Team Press Conference with Honey Alexander, March 10, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Alcoa High School Students; Governor Alexander and Richard Fulton Planting Tulip Poplar Tree at Courthouse; Remarks to Tennessee Tomorrow Students, March 11, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Leadership Meeting; ETSU Students; William Blount High School Students; Cocke County Students; Representative Dub Nance and Pages, March 12, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Betty Tenpenny and Visitors; Meeting, March 13, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Announcement of UT-Knoxville’s Condra Chairs of Excellence in Engineering, March 14, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Slides of Governor Alexander Hiking in Smoky Mountains and Rafting on Ocoee River; Candid Shots of Governor Alexander; Honey Alexander and Governor Alexander in Formal Wear, March 20, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Remarks at 39th Annual Tennessee 4-H Congress; Governor Alexander with Sara Moore Greene and Earl Shinhaster (NAACP), March 25, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Miss Piggy and Kermit the Frog Visit the Governor’s Office; Cherokee Middle School Students; Jim Henry and Roane County Interns, March 26, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Herman Wolfe and Grandchildren, March 27, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Easter at the Residence, March 29, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Luncheon with Japanese Representatives, March 31, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Governor Alexander, Jim Henry, and Pat Schroeder; Governor Alexander, Doug Henry and Presentation of Honorary Tennessean Certificate, April 1, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Honey Alexander and Carolyn Deal Discuss Day Care Options at Baptist Hospital, April 3, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Mule Day Parade, Columbia, April 5, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Homecoming ’86 Journalist Reunion; Kettering-Tennessee Conference, Better Schools, April 7, 1986 (Box 23)
    - (2 Folders) Saturn Site Dedication, Haynes Haven Mansion, Spring Hill, April 8, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Governor’s Report Radio Program with Desmond Hudson; Mock Bill Signings; Proclamation, April 9, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Benfield Elementary School Students; Service Awards, April 10, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Inaugural Ceremonies for American Airlines; Dogwood Festival; Governor’s Breakfast with Alex Haley; Copywork of Homecoming ’86 Logo, April 15, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Watt Hardison Elementary School Students; Proclamations; Overton Band Officers; Bill Signing, April 16, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Honey Alexander and Republican Party Ladies Luncheon at Residence; Governor’s Address to YMCA Youth Legislature; Corrections Administration, April 18, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Governor at Recording Session; Governor Visits Cades Cove, Hike to Abrams Falls, April 20, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Governor in Smoky Mountains, April 21, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Proclamations, April 22, 1986 (Box 23)
    - Press Conference; Honey Alexander and Republican Party Ladies Luncheon at Residence, April 24, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Photographs, Chronological
    - Governor Alexander Visits Blackberry Farm and Cades Cove, President’s Commission on Americans Outdoors Meeting, April 25, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Visit to Sam Houston Elementary School, April 28, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Press Conference Regarding Day Care Task Force; Governor Alexander and Korean Delegation; Governor Alexander at MTSU Orchestra, April 29, 1986 (Box 24)
    - (2 Folders) Governor Alexander Signing Legislation Funding Road Program with Commissioner Dale Kelley, May 1, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Cumberland College Commencement, Governor Alexander Receives Honorary Doctorate, May 2, 1986 (Box 24)
    - (2 Folders) Grand Opening of Dollywood; Governor Alexander Walking in Homecoming ’86 Crimson Clover Parade; Dedication of Boonshill Welcome Sign, May 3, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Tennessee Commission on the Commemoration of the Holocaust, Unveiling of Plaque; Wessington Place Elementary School Students and Quilt, May 5, 1986 (Box 24)
    - (2 Folders) Governor Alexander and Robin Hood Reviewing Friends Book; Governor Alexander Visits with Industrial Bank of Japan Representatives; Presentation of Certificates to Presidential Scholars Finalists, May 6, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Proclamations; Governor Alexander with ‘Just Say No’ Children, May 8, 1986 (Box 24)
    - 49th Annual West Tennessee Strawberry Festival and Parade, Humboldt, May 9, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Leadership Meeting; Event at Governor’s Residence, May 12, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Governor Alexander and Robin Hood; Tennessee Scenic Parkway Sign, May 13, 1986 (Box 24)
    - (2 Folders) School Breakfast Bill Signing; Wetlands Bill Signing; Event Honoring Ned McWherter; Career Ladder Leadership Conference; National Report Card Press Conference; Presentation of Davy Crockett Pistol; Prison Bill Signing; Seat Belt Bill Signing, May 14, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Southwestern’s 118th Annual Sales School Address; Governor Alexander and Marvin Runyon at Hume Fogg Library, May 15, 1986 (Box 24)